I want to change the way you think about
launching most Founders overthink their
first launch they think they have just
one shot at launching their product
publicly and that the messaging has to
be perfect or that no one will ever buy
or use or invest in their product
I talk to Founders constantly who
lovingly prepare their launch for months
but if you're like most startups you'll
launch something and no one will care
and if it takes you six months to get
the first version of your product in
front of anyone your startup may be dead
before you get another chance to launch
So In The Same Spirit of always be
shipping I want you to think about
launching as something that you do
continually